{
    "subject": "resource/Midnight_in_Paris",
    "predicate": "ontology/director",
    "object": "resource/Woody_Allen",
    "human_readable": "Woody Allen directed Midnight in Paris.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8650357723236084,
            "question": "Who directed the movie Midnight in Paris?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6715289354324341,
            "question": "Where was Midnight in Paris filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.664201557636261,
            "question": "What is the plot of Midnight in Paris?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6392875909805298,
            "question": "Is Woody Allen a film director?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6186655163764954,
            "question": "Name a movie directed by Woody Allen."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6087293028831482,
            "question": "What year was Midnight in Paris released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5986990332603455,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie directed by Woody Allen?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5168854594230652,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in Midnight in Paris?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48488032817840576,
            "question": "What genre is Midnight in Paris likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17355144023895264,
            "question": "Has Woody Allen won any awards for his films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Woody Allen directed Midnight in Paris.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9028_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is Midnight in Paris likely to be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9028_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in Midnight in Paris?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9028_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the movie directed by Woody Allen?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9028_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9028_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9028_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9028_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9028_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9028_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9028_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9028_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9028_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9028_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9028_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format answer:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents confirm that Woody Allen directed the movie \"Midnight in Paris\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents clearly state that Woody Allen directed \"Midnight in Paris.\" Therefore, the triple \"Woody Allen directed Midnight in Paris\" is correct according to the provided context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}